Suraj Boniwal

Software Developer

💌 surajboniwal@icloud.com 📞 +91 9974849404 in LinkedIn 🗘 Github

Software Developer with 3+ years of professional and freelancing experience in the field including analysis, design, development, testing, and deployment. Skilled, motivated, and product-oriented developer with strong Programming Concepts and design skills.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Grroom ⊘

Flutter Developer / Team Lead

May 2021 - Nov 2021 | Mumbai, India

- Coordinate the design and implementation of various applications, including collaboration with project managers, client representatives, and development teams.
- Experimented with multiple iterations during design implementation.
- · Lead a team of developers for building a scalable application.

Pixelotech &

Software Developer

Nov 2021 - Mar 2022 | Vadodara, India

- Wrote extensible and maintainable code as part of a team.
- Designed and built mobile and web applications.
- Collaborated well with other team members to determine the best design specifications and details.
- Confirmed that completed software met client requirements.
- Built Progressive Web Apps with React JS.

Arrzi

Software Developer

Mar 2022 - Present | Delhi, India

- Utilized Cloud Services for efficient building on top of AWS.
- · Managed the build and testing of mobile applications which were deployed for end-users.
- Performed routine software testing and debugging.
- · Participated in upgrading applications as well as testing and debugging.
- Provided support to the software development department.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering

Silveroak College of Engineering and Technology - 9.14 CGPA

Jun 2018 – May 2022 | Ahmedabad, India

SKILLS

Flutter Node IS

Cloud Computing

React JS Javascript

CSS

Blockchain

Python

PROJECTS

OSX ∂

Mac OS clone website using React JS

Edukate &

Online course app design using Flutter

Furballs Veterinary ∂

Veterinary app (Freelance project)

Tripma ⊘

Travel booking website design using React JS

DigitalLog &

Blog website design using React JS